Okay, it's high noon in Old Cheyenne.
Welcome to the May 19th, 2026 meeting of
the finance committee of the governing
body.
I'd like to call that meeting to order.
And if you're in the room, make sure all
your electronic devices are on silent or
vibrate. Uh when making comments online,
use the raised hand function
and all communications go through the
chair. And with that, clerk, first item.
Number 6A, application for a micro
brewery permit filed with the city
clerk's office for Joerger Hun Brewing
LLC doing business as Joerger Hun
Brewing, 3521 East Lincoln Way,
Cheyenne, Wyoming.
>> Staff report.
>> Mr. Chairman, members of the committee,
Kylie Soden, city clerk. The item before
you is an application for a micro
brewery permit submitted by Jagger Hun
Brewing LLC doing business as Jagger Hun
Brewing to be located at 3521 East
Lincoln Way. The application has been
reviewed by applicable city departments
and the Wyoming Liquor Division and the
requirements for the application have
been met. I am happy to answer any
questions you may have.
>> Any comments or questions from the
committee for Madame Clerk?
No. Okay, we'll go to public comment.
Yes, sir.
>> Uh, hello. I am Fred Hirs, owner of Yer
Hun. You have any questions for me?
>> Any questions for the applicant?
You're off easy today.
Okay. Any other public comment in the
room?
Any public comment online?
Seeing no public comment, we'll come
back to the committee. What's your
pleasure?
>> Uh, Mr. Chairman, I move to approve.
>> It's been moved by Councilman Moody,
seconded by Councilman Wolf. Any further
comments?
>> All in favor signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> Seeing there's none opposed. That vote
is unanimous. The recommendation of the
finance committee at the next meeting of
the governing body will be to approve.
Next item
>> number 10, ordinance third reading,
amending enforcement and permitting
requirements related to oversized
vehicles and making conforming
amendments,
>> staff report.
Welcome, Dr. Aldrich.
>> Good afternoon. Um Dr. Michelle Aldrich,
City Council Ward Three. Um just uh
bringing this uh ordinance amendment
back um before the committee today
again. Um there is a substitute that u
Mr. Hopinson I believe is going to
address but the uh primary focus of this
ordinance is to uh limit the number of
permits that individuals may apply for
from the police department uh to two for
um an u an ability to have their
oversized vehicles u parked um on the
street in order to load and unload those
vehicles. And um also just a reminder
that it would also uh move this from
being having to be complaint driven um
to where a a police officer who would is
driving by would be able to uh enforce
this uh rather than having it only be
complaint driven. So, those are the two
primary changes um for this and I um
would if you have any questions, I'm
sure that um Chief Francisco um or Chief
Dyron uh would be able to answer those
regarding safety of um large fire trucks
and things like that around these
vehicles. Um the difference that this
has made over the last nine months that
we've had this in place. Uh just a
reminder, this ordinance runs 5 days
before Memorial Day, which will be
coming up here shortly through 5 days
after Labor Day. Um it is so it's the
period of time actually that's reverse.
It's 5 days after Labor Day through 5
days before Memorial Day when this is in
effect. And then um we're trying to get
everything in order so that it will be
ready to go next fall when these um come
back into the community after being used
for the summer. And so with that, u Mr.
Hopinson can explain the substitute to
you as well. But I'll stand for any
questions.
>> Any
questions from the committee for Dr.
Aldrich or Mr. Hopkins,
>> Mr. Deputy Attorney,
>> Mr. Chairman, David Hopinson, Deputy
City Attorney. Um, I just wanted to
address the the substitute. Uh, this
came about as I was reviewing the
ordinance. I noted there was one area or
just one conforming amendment that
needed to be made on page nine
in subsection D.
This is the only change that the
substitute makes and it simply strikes
the language uh in that first sentence
there. It says as defined by section
8620A88 of the city code. uh that
language or that section is deleted in
this uh ordinance
and is not necessary and so that's why
that change is made.
>> Stand for any questions.
>> Councilman Wolf,
>> I'm sorry.
>> Councilman White, you got any questions?
>> No, sir. Okay,
>> I'll go to public comment in the room.
Any
public comment in the room on this item?
Any public comment online?
Okay, seeing none, we'll close public
comment and come back to the committee.
What's your pleasure?
>> Uh Mr. chairman. Um I move to approve on
third and final reading
>> and the substitute
>> and oh
>> second.
>> Go ahead.
>> Uh and um Mr. Chairman, I move to amend
by substitute the dated May 19th, 2026.
>> Second.
>> Okay. uh on the substitute. Do we have
any public comment in the
any public comment online?
>> Okay. Um back to the committee. What's
your pleasure?
>> Do you want to take a vote or do we uh
>> you have to move the the substitute?
>> Oh, I move No, I did move the
substitute.
>> Yeah. Or vote on the substitute if
you're ready.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. All in favor on the substitute
signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> And that's approved. We're back on the
main motion. Any further uh comments or
questions?
>> Uh Mr. Chair, just I I I have a quick
comment. I just wanted to thank my
colleague from Ward 3. Um I do think
that this simplifies uh things quite a
bit and makes it easier for um our
police, gives them some flexibility. as
if folks can recall when we first uh
this ordinance first came before council
was quite controversial, but I have to
say that since it's been in effect, I
think the overwhelming uh response at
least from folks that have come up to me
and thanked us for doing this has been
really positive and I think it's really
made a difference in some of the
neighborhoods particularly in Ward One
where safety truly was an issue. So, I'm
happy to support. Thank you.
Thank you. Back on the main motion. All
in favor signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> All opposed.
>> No.
>> Okay, that motion passes with Councilman
Moody. Vote no. The recommendation of
the finance committee will be to approve
the next meeting of the governing body.
Next item, please.
>> Number 11. Ordinance, second reading,
amending an solid waste fee schedule in
accordance with section 8.44.010
010 of the municipal code of the city of
Cheyenne, Wyoming, and repealing
ordinance number 4621.
>> Staff report.
>> Good afternoon, Cradle Boy. Um, public
works.
Uh, the Wyoming Department of
Environmental Quality requires mun
municipalities to update our integrated
solid waste master plan every 10 years.
The full cost accounting process was
conducted in 2019 as part of this plan
and resulted in the following
recommendation for rate increases for
fiscal year 2027. Our residential trash
and recycling at 1%, commercial trash
3%, commercial recycling at 5% and
transfer station disposal at 2%, rolloff
containers at 3%, and yard waste
services at 1%.
Um over the past now we're in the eighth
year of this plan, things seem to be
going quite well and our percentages are
holding true and hopefully we'll be able
to still be able to fund all of our
future projects that are coming up. Um
the solid waste has to pay for the
landfill expansions in the next four
years. Um, and with that said, I would
recommend approval for this fee
increase. In addition, there is a
substitute that will be coming and the
result of that substitute, I'll give a
quick brief description, was the six day
collection was double charged 3%. I must
have hit times three twice. So, this
will lower the price that I gave in the
first rendition to a little lower price.
I recommend
>> any questions from the committee for Mr.
Lavoy. Councilman Moody.
>> Thank you. Uh thank you sir. Just a
clarification. I I couldn't hear you.
Would you say the increases uh were are
proposed in here again please?
>> Yes I could say that again. Maybe I'll
mouth
>> uh through you chair. Uh the residential
trash and recycling is at 1%. The
commercial trash is at 3%. The
commercial recycling is at 5%. The
transfer station disposal is 2% and the
rolloff containers at 3% and the yard
waist services will be 1% increases.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Uh do you have any questions for Mr.
Lvoy? Councilman White?
>> No, sir.
>> All right. We'll go to public comment in
the room.
Public comment online on this item.
Okay. CNN would come back to the
committee. It's your pleasure.
>> Uh, Mr. Chairman, I move to approve on
second readings
and um,
>> going to get a second on that.
>> Oh, second.
>> Okay. Go ahead and move the substitute.
>> And, Mr. Chairman, I move to amend by
substitute dated May 14th, 2026.
>> Second.
>> Okay. The substitute's been moved by
Councilman Wolf, second by Councilman
Moody. Um, any questions or comments
from the committee on the substitute?
Any public comment in the room on the
substitute?
Any public comment online on the
Okay, back to the committee. All in
favor of the substitute signify by
saying I.
>> I.
>> Back on the main motion. All in favor
signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> No.
>> Okay. The recommendation of this finance
committee at the next meeting of the
governing body will be to approve with
Councilman Moody voting no. Next item.
>> Number 15. Ordinance. Second reading,
approving and establishing revised water
and sewer rates, tap and system
development fees, administrative fees,
service charges and penalties, and
septic and commercial waste dump rates
as recommended by the board of public
utilities.
>> Staff report.
>> Mr. Chairman and committee, Brad Bowen,
FI admin, division manager for Shyamore
Public Utilities. The ordinance before
you is to set FY2027
water rates, sewer rates, system
development fees, administrative fees,
and septic and commercial dump rates.
BOP's held public meetings where the
rates were discussed on March 16th,
April 17th, which was a council work
session, April 20th, and April 27th. The
rates are based on a thorough review of
all operation and maintenance
expenditures, debt requirements, and
review of capital plan and are not a
result of data centers or any other new
development to the committee. BOPU's
goal for FY27 rates was to move
customers to the 2026 cost of service
rates proposed in our FY24 rate study.
The rates before you include a 3% in
monthly service fee for both water and
sewer customers, residential per
thousand gallon increase of 5% for tier
1 and tier 2, and a 9% increase for tier
three and tier 4 for an overall
approximate
increase on a residential bill of
approximately 4%. Commercial and
industrial rates are set to FY206.
Cost of service and overall percentage
increases will vary based on consumption
of water compared to their discharge
into the collection system. System
development fees have increased by 5%.
Administrative fees and are reviewed on
an individual basis increased to
maintain covering costs. Septic and
commercial dump rates are increased by
5%. The overall increase is less than
the 9% proposed in our FY2026 or FY2024
rate study. The above rates support the
operation and maintenance of one water
treatment plant, two water reclamation
plants, 271 miles of raw water lines,
457 miles of treated water lines, 14
miles of recycled water lines, 327 miles
of sewer lines along with 40 ground
water wells. and I stand for any
questions.
>> Questions from the committee, Councilman
Wolf.
>> Um, thank you, Mr. Chairman, through
you. Um, thank you very much. Um could
you just kind of briefly describe the
process that you go through to examine
these rates and um sort of when you
start and then uh how that uh progresses
through
management and and the the BOPU board
and the the rate study that you referred
to in 2024. Is that something that you
update on a scheduled basis?
Good,
>> Mr. Chairman. Through you, too,
Councilman Wolf. So, the BOP budget
process starts in around January, and
during that time, what we do is each
manager reviews their division, looks at
any changes in processes
or operations that could cause a change
in expenses.
Then we go backwards and during that
same time we look at a projection of the
water usage on either a three-year or a
10-year plan depending on whether it is
related to winter months where
irrigation is occurring or during the
winter months where the use is mainly
inhouse.
Then based off of that, that kind of
gets us to how many millions of gallons
we're going to sell each year or how
many acre feet. And then that then
starts breaking down to what do we feel
is a fair increase to customers to cover
those rate increases. As far as the rate
study goes,
we had been reviewing that annually for
the last few years and getting updates
on it. When we looked at it, our
contract
came to to the end this last fiscal
year, but it gave us the rating
increases through 2030. So, in our
current budget, we have budgeted for a
new master plan. And as part of that
work, we're looking at whether or not we
piece out a separate section that is
directly related to cost of service and
looking at the rates.
>> Mr. Chairman, just one followup and and
a comment. Um, thank you. I and I asked
that question because there are voices
within our community who think that the
city council itself ought to be going
through that process. And um, knowing
how complicated rate setting is, um, I
have always responded by saying that's
really not something you want the city
council to be doing. Um, and so I
appreciate the thoroughess with which
you undertake that process. Um, the
thought that goes into it and uh, and
the complexity that's involved in
setting rates for as many customers we
have and as big a system that we have.
So, thank you very much. Thanks to you
and your staff um, and to your board for
undertaking that process.
>> Thank you. Any further comments or
questions from the committee for staff?
>> Mr. Chair, I had a question.
>> Councilman White.
>> Uh, thank you, Mr. Chair. Through you,
Brad, just looking through uh the
documents that you gave us on this item
and specifically exhibit A, uh, which
establishes the, uh, the water rate
schedules. And so when you say talk
about the increase,
I'm showing that the that the increase
would really for for a residential
structure in city um the first 6,000
gallons
currently is 5.82. And so with the
increase you're proposing, it would go
up approximately a total of
20 math was 29 cents. Uh if I have my
math correct, is that correct
or am I off
exhibit A, page two?
>> Mr. Chairman to Councilman White. I'm
doing the same quick math as you are
doing. I think that 29 cents is correct.
The number that I have on my side, and
I'll just put this a little more whole
than the way you were looking at it, is
that for a customer who uses a,000
gallons a month in water and also has
a,000 gallons a month on the sewer side,
their bill will increase by a$125.
>> Okay. Thank you for articulating that
out. Um,
you know, I'll just close my this uh be
because Councilman Wolf's correct ju all
that goes into this. I mean, it it it's
the science and the formulas that the
board of the uh public utilities
utilizes to to do these studies. Um,
it's just it's certainly not throwing a
dart at a dart board and saying, "Let's
increase it by this much." I I the work
that they put into it and the science
behind it. Um I I think generally when
they've come to us uh with this
information, it's they've certainly
justified it. So thank you, Mr. Chair.
Uh seeing that there's no more
questions, we'll go to public comment in
the room.
No. Seeing none, go to public comment
online.
Okay. Back to the committee. What's your
pleasure?
>> Uh, Mr. Chairman, I move to approve on
second reading.
>> Second.
>> Been moved by Councilman Wolf, second by
Councilman White. Any further
discussion?
All in favor signify by saying I. I.
>> Any opposed?
>> No.
The recommendation of the finance
committee at the next meeting of the
governing body will be to approve with
Councilman Moody voting no. Next item
number 23. Resolution approving the
budget of the Cheyenne Regional Airport
Board for the fiscal year beginning July
1st, 2026 and ending June 30th, 2027.
>> Staff report.
>> Uh Mr. Chairman, Robin Lman, city
treasure. A municipal code requires that
the Cheyenne Airport Board to submit a
proposed budget annually for approval by
the governing body. Accordingly, before
you is a resolution requesting your
approval of the Cheyenne Regional
Airport Board's budget for fiscal year
2027. The proposed budget is 13
million26,269
for the revenue and the proposed expense
budget is 13,42,36.
Representatives from the Cheyenne
Regional Airport Board are present to
answer any specific questions and I will
stand by for questions as well. Thank
you.
>> Questions from the committee for any
members of the board or Madame Treasure.
Not seeing any. Uh we'll go to public
comment.
Dr. Aldridge.
Chairman Esel and um finance committee
members um Dr. Michelle Aldrich, Ward 3
City Council. I just would like to
remind my colleagues that uh this is an
a budget that we have had some
discernment about and some concerns
about over the last year. We have had
repeated um reports from constituents
and concerned citizens that live in this
neighborhood regarding maintenance of
the airport parkway which in our
agreement with the airport is their
responsibility. Um I believe that thatou
is coming up for um renewal soon. Um but
I'm looking at this budget and I'm very
concerned. I know that we have new
management there and I think we can all
be excited about that. Um but there we
see a large percentage of their revenue
or a a significant amount of their
revenue is um because they lease
properties and they rent properties out.
Um
we also know that um that we have
invested as a council um well over a
million dollars uh to upgrade and update
that airport parkway um in the last
couple of years.
And uh we I did go by just last weekend
and saw that I believe now that all the
park benches have been replaced, but we
still have um signs asking people to
clean up after their dogs um and pets,
but no waste containers. Um this has
been a a source of contention with the
neighborhood and um a concern that we
took to the previous manager and to
their board multiple times. Um I and in
those conversations we've discussed
their um need to bring this budget
before us. I would just remind you that
I don't see according to this budget
where um and it is probably included in
another category but any of their
expenses for or planned expenses to
maintain um the airport parkway um I
don't see any expenses listed here um
that would indicate they're planning to
replace uh some of the landscaping that
has been allowed to die from lack of
watering um that is the gateway to our
community for people who are using air
service. We invest a large amount in the
revenue guarantee. We invest a large
amount um in the airport and um I would
just encourage you to ask lots of
questions because we can do better as a
community for our neighbors and our
constituents as well as those that are
flying in and out of our community.
Thank you.
>> Thank you, Councilman Wolf.
>> Um thank you u thank you Councilwoman
Aldridge. Um, I appreciate your are the
representatives of the airport board
here.
>> Yeah.
You would you um
just just speaking as somebody who's
been on the board for six months. I
mean, literally I I have never spent a
moment, I don't think, hearing from the
airport board, maybe once, but um I
guess I' I'd be interested to know and
and and I've been using it a lot. Uh
flying in and out of here, when it
works, it works great. And when it
doesn't, it's totally disruptive. But
that's all right. Um that's modern
travel. I I mean, sort of kind of
summarizing
just where you are in in the things that
you're doing, what your real significant
challenges are in addition to the
challenges that Councilwoman Aldridge
mentioned.
>> Would one of you like to approach the
podium and address the
questions by Councilman Wolf or you can
do it all together?
>> Hello, I'm Jennifer Nelson. I'm the
director of finance at the Shine Airport
and with me I have our new director um
Doug Bullock and I'll let him kind of
start off and then if there's any
further questions regarding the budget
I'm happy to address those.
>> Mr. Bullock
pleasure meeting you all today. Uh I've
been here about a month and I have
actually heard some of the concerns uh
specific to the Parkway and the animal
waste. So, um, I'm looking to get that
addressed in some of our processes, if
you will, on how we're going to address
that. So, I would expect some
improvements.
>> Okay. So, under the expenses, there is
some miscellaneous 72,000.
Would some of that miscellaneous funds
be used on the Parkway?
>> So, in our budget, there's a couple of
different items where that would fall
under. Obviously, our staff time um to
maintain the landscaping. That's one
area that that goes into. Um repairs and
maintenance. That covers um all of our
buildings, all of our um infrastructure
as far as the irrigation systems. Um
which has been an area that um we did
have some of our irrigation along
Airport Parkway break. Um and so that's
why um we've been working over the last
year to try to um get that fixed. Um so
it's in a couple of different areas. Um
and then under contract services, we
also have landscaping um built into that
as well.
>> Okay. Councilman Wolf, do you have a
followup?
>> Uh I do, Mr. Chairman. Thank you.
Through you.
>> Go ahead, Council Wolf. Or do you want
to comment? I
>> I
Mr. Bullock, I'd encourage you not to
sit down. Um,
I'm sorry, Mr. Chairman. Do did somebody
this other gentleman want to speak or
>> Sorry, uh, Kyle, relatively new, but
it's my understanding there is a purple
water issue as far as the irrigation to
keep some of the vegetation alive. Go
ahead, Kyle.
>> Yeah, Kyle Melino. Yeah, so we were just
informed and I'm not sure it's Boo has
any information on it, but we were told
that the purple water will not be
available this year. Um, so we get a
certain percentage and certain amount of
gallons every year to, uh, use at a
discounted rate obviously. And so this
year, uh, if that's not going to be
available, it obviously will cost the
airport quite a lot more money than we
have ever anticipated. So, um, and
Jennifer might have, you know, more
answers to you for that. So, that does
cause us a concern as well on the
landscaping that we have along Airport
Parkway. And so, uh, you know, and like
she just said, we did contribute a lot
of money to upgrading our sprinkler
system along Airport Parkway over the
last year. Uh we just turned it back on
and then we were informed about the
purple water not being available
>> and and Mr.
>> Purple water being recycled water
>> correct the reclaimed water we use
>> Mr. Chairman another question uh well
first of all welcome Mr. Bulock to the
community where did you come from
>> and then all communication goes through
the chair I know you guys are new so
>> thank you Mr. chair to Councilman Wolf.
Uh I come at it from Utah. Uh but
historically I've worked all over the
United States. I was in Utah for about
24 months helping with some issues there
at one of the airports.
>> So I I've been in the industry 28 years.
So very happy to be in China.
>> Um Mr. Chairman, for you. Um so I mean
there have been issues um with parking.
when that new terminal was first open,
it didn't appear to have enough parking.
And I guess uh one of my questions is is
that still an issue and one that you're
trying to deal with?
>> Yes, sir. Through Mr. Chairman, through
Mr. Councilman Wolf, uh yes, I've been
assessing some of our assets and
resources of the airport, some of the
needs, and it's quite easy to see that
parking is an issue. uh there are
certain days a week the uh air service
is such that the parking lot is full. So
uh we're looking at some of the
available opportunities of uh other
locations and ways to better uh resource
and lay out the parking structure.
>> Um thank you mr chairman. Just one more
question. Um but it's a big one or broad
one. Um,
so are you optimistic about the future
of this really significant uh asset to
the community and and the ability to
continue to have commercial flights here
uh on a on a regular basis?
>> Yes. Uh, Mr. Chairman, uh, Councilman,
yes. Uh, there's a lot of really great
resources here. Uh I find that there's a
actually a larger demand for air service
here in Cheyenne. And that's one of my
pet projects, if you will, over the next
couple of years is to actually increase
our air service opportunities for our
local community. Uh currently, we're
sending our tax dollars to Denver,
frankly, and I'd like to keep those
dollars local and serve the the citizens
of Cheyenne.
>> Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Uh, Councilman Wy or Councilman White,
we have the board here. Do either of you
have any questions for him?
>> I just um think thank you, Mr. Chair,
through you. Uh, Mr. Bullock, welcome.
Um, I do appreciate my colleague uh Dr.
Aldridge's uh comments. I have been at
some of those board meetings um and look
forward to uh discussing those with you.
Theou was developed back in the 80s or
or late 80s, early 90s. So, I think all
of us can agree that thatou
needs to have some significant uh
updates. And so, I look forward to
meeting you and working with you in
order to to get that done and and
address some of the um concerns that
that uh certainly are real and and some
folks in that area of town are um
irritated. So, uh, if we can, uh, come
up with some solutions, I'd certainly be
supportive of that. That said, I do
understand the importance of the
airport. Uh, my wife and I try to
utilize it all the time. It makes flying
infinitely um, more simple than having
to drive down to uh, DIA for anything.
And so, um, and to see the progress
that's been made with the with the
airlines and and how the flights are
always full, um, I think it just shows
that, you know, when you have a good
product, and we haven't always had good
products, but we I think we do now. Um,
when you have a good product, people are
going to use it, even though it might
cost just a little bit more. But thank
you. That's all I have.
>> Hey, thank you, sir.
Mr. way.
>> Uh through you, Mr. Chairman. Um I share
My name's Michael White. I share the
same sentiment about what Dr. Aldridge
said. When I come into town, I drive by
that road every day. Um I've noticed
that the irrigation system has not been
working, but uh point of order. Um the
city took it upon themselves when the
cemetery water wasn't being used for the
the recycling water. They put their own
water with domestic water. So I think
you have some options there. But when I
go by there, I see a place that the
voters voted on to bring an airport in
so people could use it. It's a pretty
sorry affair when you go down Mory
Avenue.
Regardless of the trees up until maybe a
few weeks ago, those weren't getting cut
down. It's a focal point because the
governor has his jet in his private area
over there. Um the voters voted for that
addition to that parking lot. And what
other a couple other points, how about
the fountain over there in front of the
old airport?
I believe Mr. White can reflect on some
of that because we discussed that at
length one council meeting and some of
the agreement was that the planning
department would help keep that founding
running. So recollection speaks that I
think the board, regardless if you're
new,
I think you need to do a better job. And
if we're not going to do a better job,
then I think the council needs to put an
amendment or some kind of stipulation
that says you don't get those funds
until you approve it. That's my opinion
only. Thank you.
>> Yep. Mr. White, I could probably comment
on the fountain. The historic
preservation board had put some money
into that and redone some of the
terracotta tiles. Uh there was an issue
with the pump last year. It is uh being
worked on now and the tiles are also
being worked on as well, but most of
that funding has been coming through the
historic preservation board. Sure.
>> But who's actually uh through you, Mr.
Chairman, who's actually supposed to
maintain it, the historical preservation
board or the airport board?
>> I think that's back on in the cities.
>> Okay.
>> Thank you.
>> So, Councilman Labour.
>> Thank you, Mr. Chairman. I'd like to
welcome Mr. Bullock at at a particular
pivotal moment in our airport and our
resources there that I'm very optimistic
and pleased about and that is the old
terminal.
I uh really excited to think that we're
going to take the initial step. We've
got some plans and some hopes, but the
most important thing is to replace that
roof. And that's finally going to
happen. And that is uh the essential
step that I see as being very important
there. So, I have certainly uh been
involved in these uh considerations for
some time, and I I think it it really is
something I'd like to sit down with the
uh staff and and look through the budget
and really understand it better because
it is something that the previous
administration um
uh dropped the ball.
>> I'm trying to find the word uh in a nice
way. um abandon comes to my mind and I
think that that's uh really outside of
that scope of thatou. But I also want to
point out that that's not the only
property that has landscaping issues at
the airport itself. The trees, the uh a
number of these things can probably be
dealt with and improved without a
tremendous expense and really
demonstrate that we're uh careful about
that. I'm not sure what the results
might be at the intersection of Del
Range and uh Yellowstone where we have
the elk sculpture and the scalped
landscaping which was pretty strange in
the first place but I assume that
that'll be part of the reconstruction
effort that'll be going on there but it
really is something that I think has
been adequately mentioned here that it
this is the gateway this is very
important And it's functioning and it's
functioning in a way that uh when people
I haven't used it lately but I've picked
people up there and we've seen that the
restaurants
continuing. It's a very attractive uh
facility and the landscaping needs to
reflect that as well. So, I'm hopeful I
can visit and find out more about that
budget and how that really occurs
because in that budget, I can't believe
that there isn't uh some funding for
that and and of course I have supported
and do believe in the uh uh minimum
revenue guarantee. And so a lot of good
things, but attention to detail and
working with the neighborhood. They uh
really uh
communicate very vocally to us about
that. And uh I'd sure like to report to
them that uh we're resolving it. And of
course, uh, I I know I'm very surprised
with the purple pipe recycled water and
how in the world it could be interpreted
that, uh, it's been in use for many
years that way and certainly is why we
do recycle that water and put that
piping system in. So, a lot to follow up
on, but uh again, um I think there's a
real movement here in our airport and uh
the terminal, the old terminal is really
going to pay off in the future and I
look forward to uh learning more about
the entire matter before it comes back
to us shortly here. Thank you.
>> Thank you, Councilman. Uh, does Bo have
an answer for us or can you get us an
answer by next Monday
chair, council members, Matt Bu, water
recognition division manager for BOPU.
Um, yeah, reuse is up and going. We are
running potable water through the system
right now, but it is up and running. Mr.
Bowen just looked. Um, it was not
watered last year. Um, but it is up and
running. You guys can water this year
for the the purple pipe.
>> Okay, members of the board. Okay. All
right. Thank you, Mr. Be. Any further
public comment in the room on item 23?
Any public comment online?
Okay, seeing nothing. I'll close public
comment and come back to the committee.
What's your pleasure?
>> Uh, Mr. Chairman, I move to adopt the
Shy Regional Airport budget.
>> Been moved by Councilman Moody, second
by Councilman Wolf. Any further comments
or questions?
See? None. All in favor signify by
saying I.
>> I. Seeing that that motion is unanimous,
the recommendation of the finance
committee will be to adopt at the next
meeting of the governing body. Next
item,
>> number 24, resolution supporting the
Cheyenne Regional Airport Board in its
application for an acceptance of federal
assistance from the Federal Aviation
Administration under the bipartisan
infrastructure act to assist in the
reconstruction of general aviation apron
and taxiway A1 at the Cheyenne Regional
Airport.
staff report.
Is that the board or is it our treasure?
Board. Okay. Welcome back.
>> Thank you. Jennifer Nelson, director of
finance at the Cheyenne airport. U Mr.
Chairman, through you the um this grant
um is a um part of the bipartisan
infrastructure law. Um we were granted
approximately 1.3 $1.3 million annually
totaling roughly 5.05 million over five
years to modernize infrastructure. Um
they had to be used within certain time
limits. Um part of that was to build the
passenger boarding bridge and the
remainder of those funds are used um to
uh fund the improvement of the GA ramp
and taxiway alpha at the Cheyenne
Regional Airport. Um 2 and a.5 million
of that funds like I said was for the
passenger boarding bridge and
approximately 3.1 million will be used
for the GA apron. Um the Cheyenne
airport um receives matching funds from
the state at 2 and a half% um and then
we contribute 2 and a.5% towards that
project as well.
>> Any questions from the members of the
committee for Miss Nelson?
>> Councilman Wolf.
>> Um Mr. Chairman through you. Thank you.
um
the airport. I live right up near the
airport, so I see it all the time. And
and you did a huge reconstruction of the
main runways. And so is taxi way alpha
1. Is that a is that a less significant
project than you uh undertook in the
last couple years? Miss Nelson,
>> Mr. Chairman, through you. Yes. Um so um
this portion is over um kind of near
Evans Avenue. Um so the the ramp that
goes over by our fixed base operator
Legend Aerosve. Um and then the taxi way
that leads around to um the crosswind
runway um that's the portion that's
being reconstructed. Um typically those
type of pavements um when you look at
the calculation from the federal uh the
FAA um those are lower priority um so we
receive less funds towards that and
they're less likely to be funded. The by
private and infrastructure law allowed
for less requirements um and so it was a
higher priority project um under that
law um and so we were able to to tackle
some of our pavement that we wouldn't
typically get funding for.
>> Thank you.
Okay. Any further questions for Miss
Nelson from the committee?
Okay, we'll go to public comment in the
room.
Any other public comment about the
public comment online on this item?
We'll come back to the committee. What's
your pleasure?
>> Uh, Mr. Chairman, I move to adopt.
>> Second. It's been moved by Councilman
Moody, second by Councilman Wolf. Any
further discussion?
>> Just real quick,
>> Councilman Moody.
>> Thanks, Mr. Chair. Three. Uh, thank
thank you uh, everyone. Just for the
public to know, you know, it's basic
safety, basic infrastructure. So, this
why it's very important that we do pass
this and then also going into uh,
resolution number 25. Thank you.
>> Thank you. All in favor signify by
saying I.
>> I.
>> Seeing that, that motion is unanimous.
The recommendation at the next meeting
of the governing body from the finance
committee will be to adopt next item
>> number 25 resolution supporting the
Cheyenne Regional Airport and its
application for an acceptance of federal
assistance from the Federal Aviation
Administration under the airport
improvement program to assist in the
reconstruction of the general aviation
apron and taxiway alpha 1 at the
regional airport.
>> Miss Nelson.
>> Yes, thank you Mr. Chairman, members of
the council. Um, so this is a partner
grant um for the one that you guys just
um approved to move forward. Um, this is
under the airport improvement program.
Um, they are entitlement funds that we
receive 1.3 million each year for being
a non-hub primary airport. Um, which is
defined as being more than 10,000
passengers but less than .005% of the
national passengers. Um this is that pot
of money that's a little bit more
competitive and since this is a partner
grant um we got additional funds um
because we had the original grant. Um
again the state um throws in a 2 and a
half% match and then the airport throws
in a 2 and a.5% match. Um and so the
total um cost of this project is um
6,375,000
um including both of those grants.
>> Questions from the committee for Miss
Nelson. Councilman Moody. I think it was
turn three. I think Miss Nelson wanted
to ask does this include also the fences
near the taxi ways too because we saw
what happened in uh Denver unfortunately
with somebody getting over the fence.
Does this also improve fence security?
>> Um this um excuse me through you. Um
this does not include fencing. Um but I
believe that's included um in our our
regular budget. It's not necessarily
part of the grant. Um and Kyle can
answer any questions about the security
and the fencing.
No, thank you. Because I had some people
ask, you know, some of the fencing is
kind of low. We saw what happened at
Denver International Airport a couple
weeks ago, unfortunately. But thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Uh we'll go to public comment in the
room.
See none. Any public comment online?
No. Okay. Come back to the committee.
What's your pleasure?
>> Mr. Chairman, I move to adopt.
>> Second.
>> Been moved by Councilman Moody, second
by Councilman White. Any further
comments or questions?
>> All in favor signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> Seeing that that vote is unanimous. The
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to adopt. Next item,
>> number 29B, professional services
agreement between the city of Cheyenne
and Sunrise Engineering LLC for the
Yellowstone Road and Del Range Boulevard
rehabilitation and traffic improvements
project.
>> Staff report, Mr. Engineer.
>> Good afternoon, Chairman Escoel and
members of the finance committee. Tom
Cobb, city engineer. Before you and for
your consideration obviously is this
professional service agreement between
the city of Cheyenne and Sunrise
Engineering. It authorizes them to
perform professional engineering and
surveying services to support the design
of the Yellowstone Road uh
rehabilitation project. Um this was one
of the original priority projects I
inherited back from 2015 to 2018. We're
finally implementing. Um this is for
specifically aesthetic safety capacity
and maintenance and geometric
improvements of the intersection. Um for
this process we did this is I guess I
would take this opportunity. I am
sidetracking a little bit but I want to
say to all of you that this again is a
professional services agreement. So
procurement was completed in accordance
with our city of Cheyenne purchasing
policy under qualitybased selection
which means it was solely picked on
qualifications
not price. So from that we received
eight firms originally we interviewed
three firms and selected Sunrise to do
the work for us. Um I guess I would say
to you that this process is I gets a
little confused sometimes the difference
between bidding and professional
services. So again all these are picked
based on qualitybased selection. There's
a team that was comprised of of 1%
construction planning and development um
my engineering staff and the MO. I chair
the committee but I'm a nonvote as far
as the selection process. I I think
sometimes I don't talk enough about
this, but again, we we don't just
haphazardly begin to pick these firms.
We we the selection committees are
carefully picked. Um and and they're
represented by many different
departments. So with that, I want to say
to you that the total fee for this
contract is an amount of $384,100
and it's coming from the 2015 to 2018 1%
specific purpose tax, fifth penny. And
with that, have any questions you might
ask of me? And I also have the
consultant here if you want to ask them
specific questions.
>> Any questions for members of the
committee for Mr. Cobb or the
consultant?
>> Councilman Wolf.
>> Uh thank you Mr. Chairman through you.
Um I appreciate that explanation uh Mr.
City Engineer. I mean it is critical
that we keep in mind the different ways
in which we have arrangements and
contracts with um professionals and and
also obviously acquire services um from
contractors. So thanks for letting us
know that.
>> Any further comments or questions from
the committee for either Mr. Cobb or the
consultant?
Okay, we'll go to public comment in the
room.
Public comment in the room.
See? None. Go to public comment online.
Public comment online. Okay. Come back
to the committee. What's your pleasure?
>> Mr. Chairman, I move to approve and an
amount not to exceed $384,100.
>> Second. It's been moved by council,
second by council Moody. Any other
further comments or questions?
Councilman Moody.
>> Uh, thank you Mr. Chairman through you
and thank you Mr. C for that explanation
as well. Uh, just for the public to know
you know it's very important that you
know it is for safety as you heard
there. So and again it's our duty to
make sure the roads are safe. So again
that's why pretty sure myself colleagues
will support this. Thank you.
>> Okay. All in favor signify by saying I.
I
>> I
>> seeing that that votes unanimous, the
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. Next item
>> number 31C, consideration to purchase
between the city of Cheyenne and Shannon
Chaston Enterprises Incorporated doing
business as basic equipment for the
purchase of a 240 volt split drum
vibrating vibratory vi vibratory
vibrator. Thank you. Uh roller with toe
package for the street and alley
division.
staff report.
>> Thank you. Namichek public works. That
sounds very complicated, but uh what
this is is a vibratory roller that uh is
a towbeahhind. Um it's very unique piece
of equipment and it is the first time we
will be using one of these and we are
expecting it to improve our patching
process in the rideway. Um it the uh
roller is towed behind the patch truck.
So the patch truck is full of asphalt.
This is our pothole patching process.
Um, this will this roller will provide
for better compaction because it's
heavier. Um, what we use now is a hand
roller that has to be lifted on and off
the truck every time. Um, so it might
save a few backs as well. Um, it will
provide for faster patching since it's
not required to load and unload that
hand roller. So it the uh total amount
of the purchase is 99,9959
$99,985.
I recommend approval and I'm happy to
answer any questions.
>> Any questions for director of public
works from the committee?
>> Mr. Moody.
>> Uh thanks director. Uh thank you ma'am.
Uh do you think at this time now one
will be enough? Do you think in the
future we'll need two or three?
>> Director you chair we have one patch
truck so we have one roller to tow
behind it. So at this point we're good
with one. at the in the future as road
as we get more roads I would foresee
that uh the number of equipment in all
of our situations our trucks and plows
those kinds of things will all be
required to be increased
>> any further questions for the director
from the committee
seeing none let's go to public comment
in the room public comment in the room
seeing none we'll go to public comment
online.
No public comment in line. We'll close
public comment. Come back to the
committee. What's your pleasure?
>> Uh Mr. Chairman, I move to accept the
bid amount of $99,985.
>> It's been moved by Councilman Moody,
second by Councilman Wolf. Any further
comments or questions?
>> Councilman Moody,
>> turn you. Um,
again, I think our constituents very
happy because we know we get uh Paho
complaints all the time. This will
definitely make it go uh faster and keep
our road safe. Thank you.
>> Yeah. Not not have to come back and do
it again later.
>> All right. All in favor signify by
saying I.
>> I. Seeing that that votes unanimous, the
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. Next item
number 31D, consideration of bid number
E-9-26
for furnishing one new 2026 or newer 3/4
ton crew cab, full-size pickup truck,
4x4 with a 8ft box and a fleet work
truck package for the traffic division.
Director Neichek,
>> Vicky Neichek, public works. This is a
crew cab pickup for the traffic
division. Um we have a group of five
people in the traffic division, but we
also have four seasonals. This uh
vehicle is um used for sign work. Uh it
shadows the striper when it when we're
painting. It uh helps with lane closures
for painting school crossings and road
closures. Um, we also use it during the
CFD parade and pancake breakfast
breakfast for closures. So, it's uh
fairly wellused. Um, it is part of our
uh vehicle replacement plan with its age
and mileage. And we will um the purchase
amount is uh $78,819.
We did decline the trade offer and that
was because we are going to do some
shuffling and this vehicle will end up
in street and alley and their I think
uh junk vehicle basically will go away.
So we do some shuffling when it's
possible to try to make uh make things
that are still serviceable
um work for a little longer for us.
Happy to answer any questions,
>> comments or questions from the committee
for the director.
Seeing none, we'll go to public comment
in the room. Public comment in the room.
Public comment online.
Any public comment online? Okay, we'll
close public comment and come back to
the committee. What's your pleasure?
>> I'm happy to do that. Um, Mr. Chairman,
I move to accept the bid from Fremont
Motor Company, Lander, Wyoming, in an
amount not to exceed 78,810.
>> Second.
>> Do I have a different amount?
>> 819.
>> That's the correct amount.
The correct amount is $78,819.
>> Okay, that's what it says that I
>> Oh, I'm Oh, right. So, we got it.
>> Apologize.
>> And you second.
>> I didn't say any sense, though.
>> Council. Okay. Been moved by council
Wolf, second by Councilman White. Any
further comments or discussions?
Okay. All in favor signify by saying I.
I
>> I
>> seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. Next item
>> number 31E. Consideration of bid number
E-20-26
for furnishing one new 2026 or newer
one-tonon dual rear wheels four-door cab
fullize pickup truck 4x4 with a 9- ft
utility box with crane support and a
fleet work truck package for street and
alley division.
Director Neichek,
>> Vicky Neichek, public works 7 also
sounds a little bit complicated, but um
we will use this uh um pickup truck for
removing storm grates for airing up
tires in the field, jump starting 24volt
equipment when needed, and it also holds
all of our electronic sensors for the uh
paver because we do have a a paving
machine. Um this gives us a little more
uh capabilities than we used to have by
having the crane, air compressor and
battery jump. Um we do uh function
basically as the the emergency
responders with heavy equipment in the
city. So when somebody needs uh a blade
or a loader or something like that, we
we are the ones who they call. So, um,
this will just give us some more
capabilities and I believe it's a it
would be good for the public to have
these additional capabilities to improve
our response times.
>> Questions from the committee for the
director.
>> Okay, we'll go to public comment in the
room. Public comment in the room.
Seeing none, go to public comment
online.
online public comment. Seeing none,
close public comment comment and come
back to the committee. What's your
pleasure?
>> Mr. Chairman, I move to accept the bid
in amount not to exceed $1266,662.
>> Second.
>> It's been moved by Councilman Moody,
second by Councilman White. Any further
discussion?
All in favor signify by saying I. Hi.
>> Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. Next item
>> number 31F, consideration of bid number
E-21-26
for furnishing three new 2026 or newer
halfton regular cab fullize pickup truck
4x4 with a 6'4 inch box and a fleet work
truck package for the animal control
division.
Director Fountain,
>> Eric Fountain, animal control for uh
city county. Uh we're asking for three
vehicles for consideration here to
replace uh three that we currently have.
We did have uh three trades. We're only
going to have two trades. One has a
blown engine, so nobody would accept
that trade from us at this point in
time. Um but the other two they did
accept. Um this is uh going to be all
purchased with fifth penny. There was a
little bit of consideration looking at
some general fund, but we do have enough
money in the fifth penny in order to pay
for that. We're asking for 182,98
for consideration.
>> Questions or comments for the director?
>> Question.
>> Councilman Moody.
>> Thanks, Ty. Thank you, Mr. Fountain. Um,
this would be the I support this, but I
just wanted to ask, does this include
like the Ford diagnostic program at all
or any of the upgrades to the diagnostic
program if you know at all? If you don't
I that's okay.
>> No, it does not. M or Mr. Sherman,
sorry. Sorry, Mr. Chairman through you
to Council Moody. No, it does not.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Any other comments or questions for the
director for the committee?
>> Seeing none, we'll go to public comment
in the room.
Public comment in the room.
Seeing none, we'll go to public comment
online.
No public comment online. Okay, we'll
close public comment, come back to the
committee. What's your pleasure?
>> Um, Mr. Chairman, I move to accept the
bid from Fremont Motor Company, Lander,
Wyoming, in an amount not to exceed
$182,998.
>> Second.
>> Been moved by Councilman Wolf, second by
Councilman White. Any further comments
or questions? All in favor signify by
saying I.
>> I.
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve.
Next item. Thank you.
>> Number 31G, consideration of bid number
E-22-26
for furnishing one fire rescue type 6
wildland brush fire apparatus for the
Cheyenne Fire Rescue Department.
>> Staff report.
>> Good afternoon, chair, members of the
finance committee. I'm Deputy Chief Don
Wood with Shine Fire Rescue. It's my
pleasure to request your approval of the
bid number E22-26
from HME for new wildland type 6 truck.
This is the next step forward in your
continued support of a grant which you
authorized us to pursue with the Wyoming
State Lands Investment Board. This
resolution was approved by the council
on September 8th, 2025.
The Wildland Type 6 truck is more
commonly known as a brush truck. These
trucks are heavy duty full-size pickup
trucks with a bedmounted tank and pump
designed to get into areas that your
typical fire engine cannot get into.
This truck will supplement our fleet and
ability to respond to vegetation fires
locally, regionally, and nationally.
This bid spec utilized for this truck
was sourced from the USDA uh spec for a
type six. And this particular truck is
manufactured by HME and will feature a
300-gallon tank and a 50-gallon per
minute pump. HME was the sole bid
received with an expected delivery date
of August 31st of this year. Uh, thank
you for your time and consideration and
I'll stand for any questions.
>> Questions for the from the committee to
our deputy chief.
>> I just have a quick question sir
>> to Deputy Chief Wood. Uh, Mr. Chair
through you to Deputy Chief Wood. Um,
Don, you know, when we've gotten
requests from the fire department for
trucks, usually they're two, three years
down the road. Uh, and we can get this
one actually this year. How'd you guys
manage that one?
>> Through you, Mr. Chair. Um, we've
started laying the groundwork and uh
trying to find vendors that were able to
uh perform um and have the ones that
were rolling off the assembly line. HME
uh reached out and saying that they had
three that they were in production for
and pencled our name in on uh one of the
VINs contingent on getting the grant.
So, as soon as we were awarded for the
grant, HME was already in the process of
trying to be a bidder on it. Uh we did
have a couple other vendors that were at
the bidsp spec and uh to you Councilman
White through you chair uh they were uh
asking for a delivery date to be next
year and we're trying to have this where
this money or this you piece of
apparatus we'll be able to put into our
system and be available for what we're
afraid could be a severe wildfire
season. So trying to get this be timely
and responsible and leveraging uh the
grant funds was a strong priority for
us.
>> Great. Well, good work. Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> No further questions, Mr. Chair.
>> Uh thank you, Mr. Chairman, through you.
Thank you, Deputy Chief. Um, what kind
of a what kind of a truck is this in
term who makes this truck and and and
and I assume it can be maintained by our
fleet maintenance and the the additional
maintainers that we have
>> uh through you Mr. Chair that is correct
sir. Uh this is um typically these are
based on like a Ford F550 or similar uh
type of chassis. So the actual main
body, the actual uh engine and motor of
the truck is something the fleet is
intimately familiar with. The rest of it
is a skid unit that gets mounted onto
the bed. And that has the pump and the
tank and storage spots for all of our
equipment. And those uh pumps, those
50-gallon per minute pumps are similar
to what we have on our current Wildland
Type 6. And then also uh we are re
refitting thanks to some onetime funds.
You guys allocated previously a uh other
uh full-size apparatus that we have to
have one of these skids and have a
similar type of uh uh pump located on
it. So none of these are things that our
current facilities is not able to work
on.
Oh, and thanks to uh purchasing manager
Bartleort, it's this one actually is a
uh Ford F550 that they use for their
frame. So, they do have that available.
Here's a picture um just kind of show
you guys. Like I said, it's uh pickup
truck size uh vehicle, but just
obviously our type one full-size
structure response engines are not able
to get into a lot of areas in a wildland
fire on those narrow roads.
>> Yep.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Yeah, we discussed it a
little bit last week during the fire
department's budget hearings.
Um, any other questions or comments from
the committee for deputy chief wood?
>> Councilman Moody.
>> Thank you, Mr. Chairman through you. Uh,
thank you, Deputy Chief. And just a
comment, yes, this is very important for
the public to know long may not seem
like this week, but long term it's going
to be very dry, very hot. So, we
definitely need this later on in August
when fire season will be at its prime.
So, thank you definitely for bringing
this to us.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Thank you. Hey, we'll go to public
comment in the room on this item.
Any public comment in the room?
Public comment online.
Seeing none, we'll come back to the
committee. What's your pleasure?
Mr. Chairman, I move to accept the uh
bid in amount not to exceed $343,854.
>> Second.
>> Moved by Councilman Moody, second by
Councilman Wolf. Any further discussion?
All in favor signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve.
Last item
>> number 31H, consideration of bid number
E-24-26
for furnishing one new 2026 or newer
halfton crew cab fulls size pickup truck
4x4 with a 6'4 inch box and a fleet work
truck package for the landfill division.
>> Good afternoon. Craig Lavoy public
works. Uh this 1/2 ton truck supports
our landfill for
um general maintenance operations out
there as well as transporting our staff
up to the working face and back. Uh the
price from Fremont Motor Company of
Lander was $47,031
and no cent. And we did accept a tradein
for a 2012 F-150 that's past its useful
life. And I recommend approval and stamp
for questions. Any questions or comments
from members of the committee for Mr.
Levo?
>> Question. Councilman Moody.
>> Thank you, sir. Um, just from a fleet
maintenance uh perspective, um, how
often are these uh, trucks like just
washed down? Okay. I don't mean oil
changes. I mean just regularly hosed off
after being used in the landfill and
that just so that way there's no rust.
>> Mr. Levo,
>> uh, you chairman. There's no actual
schedule. Um, they do get washed once
they, you know, it's usually when you
get rain events that gets makes it
worse, but they're they're not actually
in the working phase. They're more just
on the dirt roads and fixing and
repairing fences and such like that.
Okay. Uh, go to public comment in the
room.
Any public comment in the room?
Seeing none public comment online.
Any public comment online?
Is that thing working?
Okay.
Quiet out there. Okay.
All right. We'll come back to the
committee. What's your pleasure? Mr.
Chairman, I move to accept a bid from
Fremont Motor Company, Lander, Wyoming,
in an amount not to exceed $47,31.
>> Second. It's been moved by Councilman
Wolf, Councilman Moody. Any final
comments or questions?
All in favor signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the finance committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. And with that,
we are adjourned.